They fought World War II's greatest battle.
Air Strike is a action, drama, war film directed by Feng Xiao.
An American pilot is sent to a Chinese province to teach a crew of would-be pilots
how to fly war planes against the Japanese during World War II.
Xue Gangtou, played by Liu Ye.
Jack, played by Bruce Willis.
Steve, played by Adrien Brody.
An Minxun, played by Song Seung-heon.
Uncle Cui, played by Fan Wei.
Patriot, played by Cao Kefan.
Air Strike (Chinese: 大轰炸) also known as The Bombing or Unbreakable Spirit is a Chinese action war-drama film
directed by Xiao Feng about the Japanese bombings of Chongqing during the Second Sino-Japanese War.
The film stars Liu Ye, Bruce Willis, Song Seung-heon and William Chan, with special appearances by
Nicholas Tse, Tenma Shibuya, Adrien Brody, Simon Yam, Fan Bingbing and many others.
Mel Gibson and Vilmos Zsigmond acted as production consultants on the film.
The film explores themes of world war ii, second sino-japanese war
(1937-45), japanese occupation of china, kuomintang.
The tone is emotional.